

# VYOM GUPTA

Enthusiastic Computer Science Student from VIT, Vellore with 1.5 years+ experience in Web Development and Design. Proficient in creating user interfaces, writing and testing code, troubleshooting the issues and implementing new features based on user feedback.

## Education

2020-Present | Vellore Institute of Technology, Vellore
Bachelors of Technology,
Computer Science and Engineering
2021-Present | Indian Institute of Technology, Madras
Bachelor of Science, Data Science and Programming

#### Contact

+91 8171427101

vyom.gupta.3128@gmail.com

www.vyomgupta.me

in linkedin.com/in/vyomguptaa/

2 13/1206 Ansari Road, Saharanpur, Uttar Pradesh, India

## Experience

Shop Bonanza Pvt. Ltd | Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 **Web Developer** 

 Created an e-commerce website based on MERN Stack.

Entrepreneurship Cell, VIT | Dec 2020 - Present **Senior Core Member** 

- Lead Chapter's Technical Team of 20+ students.
- Organized E-Summit 2022, the flagship event of E-Cell, managing a crowd of 3000+ audience with a team of 65 members.

VIT Leo Club | May 2021 - Present **Member** 

 Taught 40+ underprivileged students and create awareness about education among them.

## **Projects**

#### **Flippy**

- Build an interactive trained voice bot android application based on RASA,
- Bot can create, track or cancel your order by just talking to the app.

#### CryptoBid

- Build a next gen auction website using Solidity and TruffleJS which allows user to make transactions on items using the Ethereum blockchain.
- It also provides encryption of the user's details as the user discover and bid on popular products.

## Skills

- Front-end Dev
- Communication
- Management
- Photoshop
- MS Office
- Back-end Dev
- Data Structures

### Achievements

Dec 2021 | Flipkart Grid 3.0

#### **National Finalist**

Among Top 3 National Teams in Interactive
 Voice Bot domain with over 80k+ participants.

Aug 2020 | Devfest 2.0, BITS Goa **Second Runner-Up**